原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
翻译     累
校对     累
时间轴     西·查    想念Gallifrey的Wholock
后期     累
总监     累
提特
Teeter!
是不是很惨
Is it bad?
来
Come on.
我知道  我知道
I know, I know, I know.
等我们回去
When we get back,
医生会把你治好的
the doctor, he'll fix you up just right.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
不是很惨吧
That wasn't so bad, was it?
一点也不惨
No. Not too bad at all.
你应该趁我没毁容的时候干我
You should've fucked me while I still had a face
但没关系  我们慢慢来
but that's all right, we'll work on yer timin'.
*你该走了*
*It's time for you to go*
*余生躺在桌子上*
*Lay on the table the rest of your lives*
*我属于哪里*
*Where I belong*
*你该走了*
*It's time for you to go*
拿杯水  谢谢
Can I get some water, please?
你刚才唱的那首歌
That song you just sang.
是关于什么的
What was it about?
关于死亡吧
Well... I reckon it's about death.
你了解死亡吗
You know death?
算是专家吧
Kind of a expert on it.
你看起来也像是专家啊
You look like you're kind of a expert on it too.
差不多吧
Pretty much.
既然这样  那首歌送给你
Well... then that last song was for you.
你要去哪里
Where you headed?
回家
Headin' home.
你家在哪
Where's that?
今晚的家我还没选好
Ain't picked tonight's home yet.
我能帮你选吗
Can I pick it for you?
那首歌就是我最后的倔强了
I think up on that stage is about as good as I get.
我没什么可以给你的了
I'm afraid I ain't got much left to give.
让我来吧
I'll do the giving.
如果我没这么穷困潦倒的话
If I weren't such miserable fucking company,
我肯定愿意当你的炮友
I'd damn sure take you up on that.
黄石
第三季  第九集
这才叫饼干嘛
That's how you make a fucking biscuit.
怎么了
What's wrong?
就是酸痛
Just sore.
每一块肌肉
Every muscle.
全身都疼
Every one of them.
我理解这种感觉
I know the feeling.
十年来  每次行动后我都有这种感觉
I felt like that after every op for ten years.
你没习惯吗
Didn't get used to it?
习惯了一点吧  但你不需要习惯
Little bit. But you don't need to get used to it
因为你再也不用做这种事了  对吧
'cause you're never gonna pull that shit ever again. Right?
嗯  没有下次了
No, I got that out of my system.
治疗酸痛的最好办法是睡觉
Well, the best cure for the soreness is sleep.
你继续睡觉吧  宝贝
So why don't you just go back to bed, baby?
我要带泰特去买学习用具
No, I gotta take Tate school shopping.
今晚要见老师
Tonight is a meet the teacher night,
你也要去
I want you to be there.
我在这个山谷里谁也不认识
I don't know anyone in this valley
我不想一个人去
and I don't want to be there by myself.
你就别去了
You shouldn't go at all.
我们让他在家上学吧
We should home school him.
他需要学的东西都在这里
Everything he needs to learn is right here.
全州最好的老师是他妈妈
And why do we send him to school
还送他上学干嘛
when the best teacher in the whole state is his mother?
因为他妈妈还有自己的课要教
Because his mother's got classes of her own.
我还没准备好放弃我的事业
I'm not ready to give up my career yet.
我没想让你放弃
I'm not asking you to.
但如果他的未来是管理这里的话
But if his future is running this place,
这就是他需要学习的全部
then this is all he needs to be studying.
谁来教他呢  你吗
And who's going to teach him that, you?
我爸
My dad.
他现在啥事都没有
Hell, he's got nothing else going on.
全靠我们运作
He's got us running everything.
祖父母不就是干这个的吗
That's what grandpas are for, right?
你父亲和我育儿价值观不同吧
Yeah, I don't think your father and I share the same parenting values.
他从没打过我屁股
He never spanked me once.
嗯  只是给你烙了个印
No. Just burned his brand into you.
他和当年不一样了
He was different then.
我也是
So was I.
我的看法不一样了
I see it different now.
我现在理解烙印了
I understand it.
反正我永远都不理解
Well, I'll never understand it.
你得答应我一件事  宝贝
And you gotta promise me something, baby.
答应我坚持最初的看法
Promise me you'll see that for what it was.
不要改变
Don't ever see it different.
答应我
Promise.
我答应你
I promise.
算了  我还是继续睡觉吧
Yeah, fuck it. I'm going back to bed.
什么时候开家长会
What time is this meet the parent deal?
没事
Doesn't matter.
我们不去了
'Cause we're not going.
他在农场学到的课程
The lessons he learns on this ranch,
其他学校都教不了
no school could ever teach.
我会和你父亲谈谈的
I'll talk to your father about it.
有空吗
Got a minute?
怎么了
For what?
里普有东西要给你看
Rip's got something he needs to show you.
很糟糕吗
Is it bad?
非常糟糕
Couldn't be much worse.
他在新谷仓
He's out at the New Barn.
上车吧  我送你过去
Jump in. I'll drive you down.
不  这是你和他之间的事
Nah, I think this is between you and him.
怎么了
What's going on?
我发现一个你忘记处理的东西
Found something that you forgot to get rid of.
什么东西
What's that?
他在哪里
Where was he?
在迪伦的酒吧唱歌
Singing in a fucking bar in Dillon.
我们得知道他跟什么人说了什么  凯斯
We need to know who he told and what, Kayce.
然后我来解决这个问题
And then I got to put that problem in the ground.
但是在此之前  你得告诉我
But before I do that, you're going to tell me
为什么这个问题还在呼吸
why the fuck that problem is still breathing.
在你见过的人里  属我杀人最多
You'll never meet a man who's killed more men than me.
但我从来没有杀过平民
But I ain't never murdered one.
我永远也不会
I never will.
把他带进谷仓吧
Just bring him into the barn.
走吧  出来
All right, let's go. Get out.
别走开
Stick around, Rip.
咱们就地解决
Let's just figure this all out right now.
又回到这里了  真他妈爽
Back at this fucking place. Go figure.
你答应了我
You gave me your word.
我没说出去
I kept it. I ain't said shit.
你说你要离开这个州
You said you were going to leave the state
再也不回来的
and never come back.
可你又回来了
Here you are.
我在假释中  凯斯
I'm on parole, Kayce.
每两周就要报到
I gotta check in every couple weeks
否则这辈子都得逃命了
or else I'm just running for the rest of my fucking life.
你下次在酒吧打架会怎么样  沃克
What happens when you get in your next bar fight, Walker?
警察把你按到墙上
The police got you up against the wall
你唯一可以用来交换自由的筹码
and the only thing that you can trade for
就是我们
your fucking freedom is us?
你想过吗  凯斯
Ever think about that, Kayce?
你想回来工作吗  沃克
Want your job back, Walker?
当然不想
Hell, no.
我每次转过身
This motherfucker trying to crack my skull
这家伙就想干爆我的头
every time I turn around?
我是在给你找个出路
I'm trying to find a way out for you.
你得帮我
You gotta help me, here.
你也一样
So do you.
凯斯  如果可以信守承诺  我肯定没意见
Kayce, I got no problem with a man that does what he's told.
但他做不到
But he won't.
不行  他必须得等价交换
Nah. He's gotta give us something as good as he knows.
你们想要我的把柄吗
You want something you can hold over my head?
你得证明自己  沃克
You're gonna have to prove yourself, Walker.
只要你能证明  你想走还是想留  都随你
Once you do, the choice to stay or leave is up to you.
总比死强吧
Beats dying.
在我看来  这是目前唯一的选择
As far as I see it, that's the only other option right now.
这个该死的地方
This fucking place.
就是块磁铁  把世界上所有的错误都吸引过来了
It's a magnet for everything wrong in this fucking world.
这不就把你吸回来了
Well, it drew you back.
你犯了什么错
What's wrong with you?
过了这村没这店了
I ain't gonna offer it again.
门开着  进来吧
Door's open. Come on in.
原谅我的穿着
Pardon the way I'm dressed.
我刚做完瑜伽
Just finished my yoga.
穿着长袍吗
In a robe?
我裸体做的
Do it naked.
衣服会限制身体的自然运动
Clothing restricts the body's natural movement.
如果我们按照上帝创造我们的方式生活
It'd be a better world if we went about our days
世界会变得更美好
just the way God made us.
请坐
Have a seat.
怎么样了
So how's it going?
我们把他们逼得很紧
We've been pushing them pretty hard.
很好  继续努力
Good. Keep pushing.
我不想回监狱
I ain't trying to go back to prison
也不想被杀
and I ain't trying to get killed.
你们所做的一切都是合理的
Everything you've done has been justified:
他们骚扰我们的牲畜  你们把他们赶走了
they harassed our livestock and you ran them off.
如果上了法庭  这就是宣判结果
That's the way this will play out in a court of law.
继续逼他  让他做出我们可以在法庭上利用的事
Now keep pushing until he does something else we can use in court.
我再找点人来
I'm going to bring some more men on.
我可不希望他找十几个牧人
I don't want a dozen of his wranglers
把我拖进灌木蒿丛
dragging me through the sagebrush.
随你啊
Bring on whoever you like,
最好有人能被拖进灌木蒿丛
but somebody had better get drug through the sagebrush.
如果没有任何损失  我们就不能起诉要求赔偿
We can't sue for damages if there aren't any damages.
你没我那么了解约翰·杜顿
You don't know John Dutton like I do.
所以我付你那么多钱嘛
That's why the job pays so well.
继续逼那个混蛋
So keep poking him till that son of a bitch
让他做一些无法挽回的事情
does something he can't take back.
走吧
Let's go.
怎么回事
What the fuck happened?
那些业余牛仔
Those dude-string cowboys.
她需要医生
She needs a doctor.
好吧  来  给我
Okay, come on. Give her to me.
他们骑着马  想把我们踩死
They ran us down on horses. Tried to trample us to death.
罗伊德  叫兽医
Lloyd, call the vet.
抱歉  先生  你不吃早餐吗
Sorry, sir. You're not eating breakfast?
嗯  我今天起晚了
No, I slept in today.
我最后再说一遍  我有一种预感
For the last time, I got a feeling.
可以来点巧克力黑猩猩麦片吗
Can I have some Choco Chimps?
好的
Yeah, sure.
听起来不错
That sounds pretty good.
来两份吧  盖特
How about two of those, Gator?
你不想吃美味的熏肉吗  或者我
You don't want some tasty bacon or I got--
不了  我今天就吃巧克力黑猩猩麦片
No, I think Choco Chimps this morning.
看来我不是唯一嗜睡的人啊
Seems I'm not the only one sleeping in these days.
我的闹钟没响
My alarm didn't go off.
你为什么要设闹钟
And why... why are you setting an alarm?
我妈妈就是我的闹钟
My mom's my alarm.
不管我喜不喜欢  她早上6点就响
She goes off at 6:00 A.M. whether I like it or not.
今天她没起来
Today, she slept in.
天啊  我爱夏天
God, I love summer.
我也是
I do, too.
可惜夏天会结束
I hate for it to end.
是啊
Yeah.
事先声明
This is, for the record--
没事的  盖特
It's going to be fine, Gator.
-牛奶  -一点点就好
- Milk? - Just a little.
能让我先吃完早饭吗
Can I finish my breakfast?
这很重要
It's important.
我以为你上班去了呢
I thought you were at work.
今天帮我个忙  伙计  待在屋里  好吗
Do me a favor, today, buddy, and stay inside, okay?
房子里吗
Inside the house?
是的  看个电影什么的
Yeah, just... Watch a movie or something.
我吃完早饭就过去
I'm going to finish my breakfast, then I'll be down.
在谷仓等我
Meet me at the barn.
有点不对劲
Something's wrong.
看起来是的
Looks that way.
麦片要软了
It's gonna get soggy.
这么糟糕啊
That bad, huh?
本来可以更糟  但也糟不到哪去
Could have been worse, but not much.
需要步枪才能搞定吗
And it takes rifles to fix?
可能吧
It might.
出去吧
Let's go outside.
那个流浪汉什么时候回来的
When did that drifter wander back?
今天早上
This morning.
和他有关吗
He involved in this?
这是两码事
It's two separate things.
他们怎么了
What happened to them?
是你朋友韦德·莫罗干的  先生
Your friend Wade Morrow's what happened to them, sir.
用马踩了他们
He ran them down.
在我们的地盘上
On our side of the fence.
牧人们很不爽  想去找他们算账
Boys are pretty hot. They want to go after them.
他来这儿就一直在找我们麻烦
He's been goading our ass ever since he got here.
我也觉得很烦
He's been goading me pretty good, too.
那家伙是个恶棍和懦夫
That piece of shit is a bully and a coward,
但他不傻
but he ain't stupid.
他的工作不是让游客骑野牛
His job ain't riding tourists by buffalo.
这就是他的工作
This is what he was hired to do.
先生  你想怎么办
Well, sir, what do you want to do?
不能打电话给治安官
Can't call the sheriff.
嗯  他们已经考虑到了
No, they've already thought about that
肯定有了理由  借口或不在场证明
and already have a reason or an excuse or an alibi.
我们得做点什么
We got to do something.
没有人比我更想找那混蛋算账
I have more reason than anyone to go after that piece of shit.
你不能让他们鲁莽行事
You don't send them off half-cocked.
你得聪明点
You be smart about this.
想出一个可行的计划
You figure out a plan that works,
把那个垃圾送去火车站
and you take that trash to the fucking train station.
遵命
Yes, sir.
里普
Rip.
那狗娘养的拿了我的东西
That son of a bitch has something that belongs to me
我想拿回来
and I want it back.
三十年到无期徒刑
一次谋杀
四次袭击
囚犯姓名
加勒特·兰德尔
地址
蒙大拿州  雷德洛奇市  巴克霍恩草地1401号
舒瓦茨和梅耶
达顿小姐
Miss Dutton, there's, um...
那是我的桌子
That's my desk.
不  现在是我的桌子了
Not anymore. It's my desk now.
我的电脑  我的办公家具
My computer. My office furniture.
我的办公室
My office.
牛仔有句话怎么说的来着
What's that saying cowboys use,
"敢惹公牛  就是找怼"
"fuck with the bull and you get the horns."
谁让你惹公牛了呢
Well, you fucked with the bull.
你在镜子前肯定练过这句话吧
I bet you practiced saying that in front of the mirror.
练了一个小时  任何事我都会准备周全
For an hour. I prepare for everything.
预期所有可能的结果
I anticipate every possible outcome.
我对你也是抱有同样的期待
And I would have expected the same from you,
但如果你动动脑子
but if you had given this any thought,
就会知道所有可能的结果
you would have known every possible outcome
都是让我坐在这里
leads to me sitting right here.
当你发现自己站在要塞的墙上时  威拉
When you find yourself standing on the wall of the Alamo, Willa,
结果就已经决定了
the outcome has already been decided.
唯一要做的就是在他们杀了你之前
The only thing left to do is to kill as much as you can
尽可能多地杀戮
before they kill you.
有理
I respect that.
你也斩获颇丰啊
And you certainly got your kills.
你这个小婊子
You little bitch.
害我的股东损失了数十亿美元
Cost my shareholders billions.
但现在因为这件事
But now, as a result,
我的股东变成了舒瓦茨和梅耶的大股东
my shareholders are majority owners of Schwartz and Meyer.
而你  被解雇了
And you, you're fired.
谢谢你在你父亲农场周围买的土地
So thank you for all that land around your father's ranch.
我们对这个山谷有宏大的版图
We have big plans for this valley.
在这种刺痛感消退后  给我打个电话
And after the sting of this fades, you should give me a call.
有了你  我肯定如虎添翼
You could do very well working for me.
当这一切结束后
When all this is over...
我要把你的文凭挂在我招待所马桶的上方
I'm gonna hang your diploma above my toilet in my guest house.
我向你保证
You have my word.
我说了  你得先等刺痛感消退
Like I said, you gotta let the sting fade.
然后我们可以谈谈
Then we'll talk.
我的刺痛感永远不会消退
The sting never fades with me.
这是一个痛苦的教训
It is a painful lesson.
下次就轮到你了
And one you're about to learn.
我真的很喜欢她
I really like her.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你是加勒特·兰德尔吗
Are you Garrett Randall?
谁找我
Who wants to know?
蒙大拿州的检察长
The attorney general of Montana.
这是你的老板吗
That who you work for?
这是我本人
That's who I am.
你找我干嘛
What do you want with me?
我只是想看看你
I just want to look at you.
看看有没有我的影子
See if I recognize anything in myself.
迈克
Michael?
这不是我的名字了
That's not my name anymore.
虽然你不承认
Well, that might not be what you call yourself
但这就是你的名字
but that's your name.
让我看看你
Let me look at you.
你的眼睛像你母亲
You got your mother's eyes.
别跟我提你杀的那个女人
Don't you mention the woman you killed to me.
看来你都查清楚了
I see, you got it all figured out, huh? You...
你都知道了
you know the score.
我和你母亲当时毒瘾很大
Your mother and I were strung out on so much shit.
有时我躺着看着天花板
I'd lie there some times, I'd stare up at the ceiling
还以为天花板在我身上融化了呢
and think the son of a bitch was melting on top of me.
但我们曾经也怀揣过希望
But at one time, we had hope.
我们梦想着未来
We dreamed about a future.
该死的毒品夺走了我们的一切  所以
Those goddam drugs took it all away from us, so...
你为什么这么做
Why did you do it?
你不需要知道
You don't need to know that.
我需要
Yes, I do. I need it.
为了我的灵魂
For my soul.
我想知道我到底是谁
To understand who the hell I am!
你想知道你是谁
You wanna know who the hell you are?
你母亲为了毒品出卖了她的身体
Your mother sold her body for drugs
所以我杀了她
and I killed her for it.
这就是你
That's who you are.
这就是你的母亲
That's where you come from.
看看你都变成什么样了
Look what you've made of yourself.
你母亲曾经有过美好的一面
See, there was good in your mother at one time.
她有优点  我也有优点
Good. There's good in her, good in me, too.
谢天谢地  你继承了我们的优点
Thank God those are the parts of us that he gave to you.
我可以说对不起  但如果没发生这些事
I'd say I'm sorry, but if things hadn't happened
你要么已经死了
the way they did, you'd be dead,
要么进监狱  要么和我一起焊接管围栏
you'd be in prison or you'd be welding pipe fence with me.
你走上了属于你的道路
You got put on the road you belong on.
继续前行吧  儿子
You stay on it, son.
约翰·达顿不该告诉你的
John Dutton never should have told you.
他没有
He didn't.
是我自己发现的
I found out myself.
好吧  真可惜
Oh, well, that's a shame.
现在你想了解我了
Now you're gonna want to know me.
我杀死了我所爱的一切
I've killed everything I ever loved
以及爱我的一切
and everything that ever loved me.
你不会想了解我的  儿子
You don't want to know me... son.
我必须了解你
I need to.
我从来不知道我是谁
I've never known who I was.
我一直觉得自己不完整
I've never felt like I was whole.
我必须了解你
I need to know you.
否则我将永远不了解自己
Or I will never know myself.
喝咖啡吗
You want some coffee?
好的
Sure.
来
Come on.
你得走了
You need to go.
吉米  怎么了
Jimmy, what happened?
我不能说
Can't really talk about it.
好吧
Okay,
我们先去波卡特洛的牛仔竞技赛  然后去奥格登
we're headed to the rodeo in Pocatello, then Ogden.
我们要是过来的话  就给你打电话
I'll just call you when we swing by this way.
你是哪里人
Where'd you come from?
无名之地
Nowhere.
生活就是喜欢找麻烦
Life just likes to hunt up fucking trouble.
一直找上我的门
Throw it at me.
诗人啊
A poet.
走吧
All right, let's go.
好了  起来  我们走
All right, get up, let's go.
别做傻事
Don't do anything stupid.
你们得离开这里一会儿
Y'all need to stay clear of here for a little while.
-明白吗  -嗯  吉米说过了
- You understand that? - Yeah, I got the memo.
吉米  我们走
All right, Jimmy, let's go.
你  我们走
You, okay, let's go.
你不用过来
You don't have to come.
不  我绝对不能错过
Oh, no. I wouldn't miss this for the fucking world.
是吗
Yeah?
我感觉这里正在失去光彩
This place is losing its luster to me.
我觉得可能还有点光彩
I don't know, I think there might be a little luster left.
他们还不明白我们的意图
They're sure slow to get the message.
我们把人都叫上来
Yeah. Maybe we ought to get the boys up here
再去招惹这群混蛋吧
before we mess with these assholes any more.
这他妈就一个人
It's one fucking guy.
我们的工作就是找麻烦  我们找点麻烦吧
You know, we're getting paid to stir trouble, let's stir some.
操  克林特  掉头
Shit! Clint, turn back!
杀了你们这群狗娘养的
I'll shoot every one of you sons of bitches!
死得这么痛快  便宜你了  混蛋
You got off easy, you piece of shit.
坐在这里吃晚饭感觉挺别扭的
Feels wrong, sitting here eating dinner
-我们应该去处理  -凯斯
- when we should be down there dealing with-- - Kayce.
处理什么
Dealing with what?
你今天过得怎么样  亲爱的
How was your day, honey?
我被炒了
I got fired.
这件事也不用详谈了吧
I guess we won't talk about that either.
让我们继续幻想
Let's just continue with the illusion
我们是一个幸福的大家庭
that we're one big, happy family.
这个家庭就是一个幸福的大家庭
That's exactly what this family is.
原来的确是
Well, that's exactly what it was.
现在嘛  我都不知道该用什么词形容了
I don't know what the fuck to call it anymore.
-够了  我受够了  -不  拜托
- That's it. That's fucking it. - No, please.
还是我走吧
Allow me.
泰特  走吧
Come on, Tate. Let's go.
这就是我们不在晚饭时谈论公事的原因
And that's why we don't talk about business at the dinner table.
以后不会了
Won't do it again.
我去看看泰特
I'll go check on Tate.
去吧
You do that.
走  杰伊  让他快点
Let's go, Jay, keep his ass moving.
快点  快点
Come on. Come on.
快点
Come on.
给我一个名字
I need a name.
什么名字
What name?
雇佣你的混蛋
The motherfuckers that hired you.
我不会再问第二遍
I'm not gonna ask you again.
直接开始凌迟
I'm just gonna start cutting shit off of you.
罗尔克
Named Roarke.
市场股票的混蛋
Market Equity son of a bitch.
放我下来
Let me down.
为什么
Why would I do that?
我要杀了你  你这个狗娘养的
I'm gonna kill you, you son of a bitch.
但是在此之前  我要拿回一个东西
But before I do, I'm gonna take something back.
你不配拥有这个烙印
You don't deserve to wear this fucking brand.
沃克  来
Walker, over here.
这是你最后的机会
This is your last chance.
证明自己  得到我们的信任
You prove yourself and you have our trust.
如果你不愿意
You turn your back on me now
我就从你身上也拿点东西
and I'm gonna take something from you, too.
先生  我不认识你
Mister, I don't know you.
但如果你有这个烙印  肯定是个坏人
But if you're wearing that brand, you must be a bad man.
既然这群狗娘养的想要回去  那你肯定坏透了
And if these motherfuckers want it back, you must be even worse.
因果报应以各种形式和大小出现
Karma comes in all shapes and sizes.
看来今天就是我了
Looks like it's me today.
你们按住了
Y'all best hold him.
好
All right.
你们想报仇  现在报了
You all wanted revenge. Well, now you got it.
但报仇是要付出代价的
But there's a price to pay for revenge.
你们得付出代价
Now you gotta pay it.
他们没事
They're all fine.
对不起
Sorry... to, uh...
我在餐桌上提起这件事
to bring that up at the dinner table.
这种事本来就不应该出现
Well, there shouldn't be things like that
当然也就不用提起了
to discuss in the first place,
但这就是生活
but that's life.
如果你没有注意到  生活就是残酷和漠然的
In case you haven't noticed, it is cruel and uncaring.
你无法跟邪恶讲理  儿子
You can't reason with evil, son.
邪恶想要什么就会索取  而且不会停止
Evil wants what it wants and won't stop
直到胜利或者被消灭
until it's won or you kill it.
消灭邪恶的唯一方法就是比它更卑鄙
The only way to kill it is to be meaner than evil.
这是你的最后一课  儿子
That's going to be your last lesson, son:
如何比邪恶更卑鄙
how to be meaner than evil
但仍然爱着你的家人
and still love your family.
还可以享受日出
And still enjoy a sunrise.
怀俄明州
永远的西部
为什么你们都把尸体扔在这里
Why y'all dump them here?
因为这里一百英里之内没有人住
'Cause no one lives within a hundred miles.
这个县没有人  没有治安官
It's a county with no people, no sheriff,
也没有同龄的十二个陪审员
and no twelve jurors of your peers.
你们在那里一共扔了多少具尸体
So how many people y'all dumped out there?
周围三个州的人
Everyone from three states around
所有的秘密都被扔下了那个悬崖
dump their secrets off that cliff.
你想知道西部是怎么开拓的吗
You want to know how the west was won?
峡谷底部的骷髅就是答案
The skeletons at the bottom of that canyon is how.
你现在得想办法不要成为他们的一员
Now all you gotta do is figure out how to not be one of them.
提特
Teeter.
准备好了吗
You ready?